Guide to the Council of School Supervisors and Administrators Records WAG.269
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files, 1945-2007
  - Convention, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Convention, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Convention, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Convention, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Convention, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Convention, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Convention, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Convention, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Convention, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Convention, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Convention, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Convention, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Convention, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Convention, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Convention, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Convention, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Convention, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Convention, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Convention, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Convention, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Convention, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Convention, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Convention, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Coordinating Committee, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University School of Labor Relations CSA Focus Groups for Collective Bargaining: Bronx, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University CSA Focus Groups: Brooklyn, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University CSA Focus Groups: General, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University CSA Focus Groups: Manhattan, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University CSA Focus Groups: Office of School Food and Nutrition Services Bills, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University CSA Focus Groups: Queens, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University CSA Focus Groups: Staten Island, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Council of Administrators and Supervisors, Local 12: Convention, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - CSA Change, Jun 1992 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - CSA Directory, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - CSA Staff Development Work Shops, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Cuomo, Mario M., 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Day Care Center Liaison Committee, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Day Care Unit, 1972-1977; 1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Decentralization: Ad Hoc Committee, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Decentralization: African American Teacher Association, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Decentralization: A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Decentralization: Association of Assistant Principals, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Decentralization: Board of Education Agreements and Statements (with UFT and CSA), Sep-Nov 1968 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Decentralization: Board of Education CSA Meetings with Superintendent Bernard Donovan, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Decentralization: Brandeis High School, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Decentralization: CBS Television Bulletins, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Decentralization: Clippings, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Decentralization: Clippings, 1972-1981 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Decentralization: Commentary on, 1984; 1986; 2002 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Decentralization: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Decentralization: CSA Flyers, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Decentralization: CSA Position Paper (Toward Action and Change: Decentralization), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Decentralization: CSA Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Decentralization: Demonstration Districts, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Decentralization: District 6 (Meeting Minutes), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Decentralization: District 10 (Meeting Minutes and Notice of Special Meeting with John Doar), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Decentralization: District 11 (Talk given to local School Board), Sep 1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Decentralization: District 23 (Clippings), 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Decentralization: District 24, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Decentralization: District 25, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Decentralization: District 26, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Decentralization: District 27, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Decentralization: District 28, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Decentralization: District 29, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Decentralization: District 30 (PTA Bulletins), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Decentralization: Districts (General), 1968; 1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Decentralization: Districts Clippings (I), 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Decentralization: Districts Clippings (II), 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Decentralization: Districts (Two Bridges Model), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Decentralization: Dodge Vocational High School, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Decentralization: General, 1962; 1967-1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Decentralization: Hearings, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Decentralization: High School of Fashion Industries, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Decentralization: I.S. 201 Dispute (Clippings), 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Decentralization: John V. Lindsay, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Decentralization: Legislation, 1962; 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Decentralization: Legislative Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Decentralization: Local School Boards, 1966-1969 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Decentralization: Meeting, CSA and Civil Service Organizations, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Decentralization: New District, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Decentralization: New York Civil Liberties Union, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Clippings), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Clippings), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Clippings), 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Coalition for Community Control), 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (General), Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (General), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (General), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (General), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (General), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Jerald E. Podair), 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Litigation, Appeals), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Litigation, Clippings), 1967-1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Litigation, CSA v. Board of Education, Kings County Supreme Court), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Litigation, Rankin v. Shanker et al., New York State Supreme Court), 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Litigation, Research), 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Litigation, Rodriguez et al. v. Sklar, U.S. Southern District of New York), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Racial Quotas and Excessing, Litigation and Clippings), 1968-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Research Material), 1967-1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Decentralization: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Reports on Junior High School 271), 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Decentralization: Other Organizations, Sep-Nov 1968 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Decentralization: Principal Requests, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Decentralization: Public School 148, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Decentralization: Public School 202, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Decentralization: Resolution of the Catholic Teachers Association of the Diocese of Brooklyn, circa 1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Decentralization: School Crisis Hotline, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Decentralization: Scope Bulletin, Sep-Oct 1968 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Decentralization: Short Range Plan (Board of Education), Sep 4, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Decentralization: Strike (Clippings), 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Decentralization: Summer 1968 Fact Sheet (CSA) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Decentralization: Television and Press Coverage and CSA Replies, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Decentralization: United Federation of Teachers, Flyers and Pamphlet, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Decentralization: United Federation of Teachers, Publicity, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Notes and Lists, Undated; 1968 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook "Decentralization Crisis Jan 1969-Jul 1969" (I) (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook "Decentralization Crisis Jan 1969-Jul 1969" (II) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook "School Crisis Sep 1-28, 1968" (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook "School Crisis Nov 1968-Jan 1969 (I)" (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook "School Crisis Nov 1968-Jan 1969 (II)", 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook "School Crisis 3: Oct 1968-Nov 1968" (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook "School Teacher Strike 2: Sep 26, 1968-Oct 22, 1968" (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Decentralization: Zuckerman Scrapbook (untitled), 1968-1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Demonstrations at City Officials' Homes, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Directory: Association of New York City Schools, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Directory: New York City Public Schools, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Directory: Supervisors and Administrators, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Discrimination against Jewish Applicants: Anti-Defamation League Report, etc., 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - District Chairmen, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - District Chairmen, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - District Chairmen, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - District Chairmen, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - District Chairmen, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - District Chairmen, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - District Chairmen, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - District Chairmen, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - District Chairmen, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - District Chairmen, 1990-2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - District Chairmen: Handbook, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - District Chairmen (Chairpersons): Handbook, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - District Chairmen's Meetings with Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - District Chairmen's Weekend, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - District Chairmen's Weekend, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - District Chairmen's Weekend, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - District Consultation Committee (Sidney Zelman, CSA District Chairman), 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - District Meetings' Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Division of Curriculum and Instruction: Science, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Dual Job Income Limitation, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - East New York Community Corporation: Education Committee, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Edley, Christopher: Community and Group Tensions (PA Society of Newspaper Editors), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Educational Policies Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Eight Days (Small Group Workshops), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Junior High School, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 20a)
  - Elections, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Elections, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Elections, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Elections, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Elections, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Elections, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Elections (I), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Elections (II), 1977 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Elections, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Elections, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Elections, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Elections, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Elections, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Elections, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Elections, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Elections, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Elections, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Elections, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Elections, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Elections, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Elections: Administrators and Supervisors for a Concerned Union, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Elections: Peter O'Brien Election Scrap Book (Zuckerman), 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Elections: Ted Elsberg and Blanche Schwartz, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Elections: Warshaw, Weinstein Case (re: 1971 Election), 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Elections: Zeichner Case, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Elementary School Principals Association, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Escuela: Edicion Escuela Elemental, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Ethics, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Ethnic Data, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ethnic Integration, 1972-1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Ethnic Personnel Issues: Clippings, 1972-1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Ethnic Personnel Issues: General, 1972-1977 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Ethnic Surveys, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Ethnic Surveys, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Ethnic Surveys, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Ethnic Surveys (I), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ethnic Surveys (II), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Ethnic Surveys (I), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ethnic Surveys (II), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Ethnic Surveys, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Ethnic Surveys (Gerry Report; HEW), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations Supervisory Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Executive Development Institute for New Elementary School Principals: Training Workshops for New Principals, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fernandez, Joseph (Chancellor), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Finances, 1968-1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fleischmann Panel Report: Clippings (Community Control), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ford Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fordham University: Program for Developing Instructional Administration of Urban Schools, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - General Membership Meetings: Minutes, 1968-1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - George Washington High School: Conflict with Community Activists, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Gifted Education Committee, 1977; 1981-1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Gladstone, Irving Arthur: Dr. I. A. Gladstone Reflections, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Governance of New York City School System: Mayor Abraham D. Beame Plan, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Grade Organization Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Grievances, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Griffith, Hugh N., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Heads of Associations Meetings, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Heads of Associations Meetings, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - High School Consultation Committee: Minutes, 1975; 1976 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - High School Diploma Requirements Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - High School Principals and Vocational High School Principals Association, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - High School Supervisors Report, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - History of the Council of Supervisory Associations, 1962-1965 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - History Fairs (New York City and National), 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Hotline Messages, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hotline Messages, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Hotline Messages, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hotline Messages, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hotline Messages, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hotline Messages, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hotline Messages, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hotline Messages, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hotline Messages, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Hotline Messages, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hotline Messages, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Hotline Messages, Jan-May 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hotline Messages, Jul-Dec 1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hotline Messages, Jan-Apr 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Hotline Messages, May-Dec 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hotline Messages, Jan-Jul 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Hotline Messages, Aug-Dec 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Hotline Messages, Jan-Apr 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Hotline Messages, May-Jul 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - House of Delegates, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - House of Delegates, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - House of Delegates, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - House of Delegates, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - House of Delegates, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Hurwitz, Howard (Ridgewood Times Clippings and Calendar), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Illiterate Principals (Clippings), 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Illiterate Principals (Public Relations), 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Indigents: Representation of before Administrative Agencies, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - In-Service Planning Committee, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Internship Program (Assistant Principals), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Jamaica High School: Jeffrey Schwartz Case and Other Civil Liberties Issues, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Joint Association of Supervisors, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Junior High School Association (New York), 1969; 1974; 1978 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Junior High School Association (New York), 1981; 1988 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Labor Day Parade, 1993; 1998 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Law License Requirements Committee, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Law License Requirements Committee, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1968; 1970 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Layoffs and Excessing (I), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Layoffs and Excessing (II), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Layoffs and Excessing (III), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Layoffs and Excessing, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Layoffs and Excessing: O'Brien v. Board of Education (NYS Supreme Court), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Layoffs and Excessing: Transfer Policy Litigation and Research, 1969-1983 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Layoffs and Excessing: Seniority Lists, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Legal Cases: Board of Education v. CSA (NYS Supreme Court), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Legal Cases: Various, 1973-1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Legal Cases: Various, Appeals, 1969; 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Legal: Frankle and Greenwald, General, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Legal Representation of Indigent Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Legal Research, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Legal Services Prepaid Program, 1977; 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Legislation (I), 1969-1976 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Legislation (II), 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Legislation (III), 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Letterhead, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Levy, Jill (President), 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Managerial Status for Principals, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Manpower Development, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mansfield Decision, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Master Teacher Position, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Members in Leadership Positions, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Membership, General, 1974-1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Membership, Application, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Membership, Mailings, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Music Educators' Conference, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 12a)
  - National Association of Secondary School Principals, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - National Commission on Excellence in Education, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1971; 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Negotiating Committee: Contract Negotiations Transcripts, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Negotiations, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Negotiations (I), 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Negotiations (II), 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Negotiations, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Negotiations, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Negotiations: Honest Ballot Association Contract Ratification, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Nepotism, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - New York City Bicentennial Commission and Celebration, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - New York City Citywide Reading Program (Draft report, Huron Institute), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1962-1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1992-1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 1997-2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - New York City Elementary School Principals Association (NYCESPA), 2003-2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - NYCESPA: Newsletters, 1956-1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - NYCESPA: Newsletters, 1983-1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - NYCESPA: Newsletters, 1998-2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - NYCESPA: Newsletters, 2005-2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - New York City Parent Guide, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - New York City Teachers Retirement Board, 1972-1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - New York City Temporary Commission on Education: Final Report to Mayor Abraham Beame, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - New York State Education Department, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)